该死!
Son of a bitch!
Jin 快 醒醒 伙计
Jin. Come on. Wake up, buddy.
醒醒
Wake up.
Sawyer啊
Sawyer.
我睡了多久?
How long have I been out?
一会儿
A while.
我想你应该歇够了
Figured you could use the rest.
Claire和Locke... 他们呢?
Claire and Locke... where are they?
不知道 他们之前说会在日出前回来
I don't know. They said they'd be back by sunup.
- 在他们回来之前 我们得赶紧离开 - 冷静点 喔 喔
- We have to get out of here before they come back. - Easy. Whoa, whoa.
我投靠Locke了
I'm with Locke.
那不是Locke
That is not Locke.
嗯 我知道
Yeah, I know.
无论他是谁 他说他能把我们带出这该死的小岛
Whoever he is, he says he can get us off this damn island.
我不能走
I can't leave.
Sun还不知在岛上哪个角落呢
Sun could be here somewhere.
好吧
Fine.
我答应你 如果她在岛上 我们绝不离她而去
If she's here, you got my word. We ain't leaving without her.
什么声音?
What's that?
他们回来了
They're back.
嗨
Hi.
你来了
Hi yourself.
啊
Ahh.
喔
Wow.
Jimmy啊...
Jimmy...
嗯
Mmm.
你真是...
You are...
太厉害了
unbelievable.
嗯
Mmm.
宝贝 你和我不分伯仲
You weren't too shabby yourself, darlin'.
嗯
Mmm.
宝贝?
Baby?
嗯?
Yeah?
9点的时候 你不是要和那个人碰头吗?
Aren't you supposed to meet that guy at 9:00?
嗯 然后呢?
Yeah. So?
现在是8点...
It's 8...
42分
42.
该死!
Damn it!
我本来不想让你看见的
You weren't exactly supposed to see that.
Jimmy 你拿这么多钱要干什么?
Jimmy, what are you doing with all that money?
这次会面 有可能做成一笔交易
This meeting is a potential investment.
我们约定五五分账
We're going 50/50.
那家伙想先看到钱
The guy wants to see the money upfront.
别担心 不会太久的 我马上回来
Don't worry. It won't take long. I'll be right back.
然后我们就去兜风... 喔
Me and you'll go for round... Whoa.
离箱子远点
Step away from the case.
别乱来 宝贝
Take it easy, honey.
帅哥 有件事我得告诉你
Here's the thing, dimples.
我知道骗子的花样 我前夫就是骗子
I can spot a con man. I'm married to one.
所以我知道你们那些伎俩
So I know all about the pigeon drop.
哦 你刚说啥? 那箱子是偶然打开的?
Oh, what? That case just accidentally flew open?
你以为我笨得像头猪?
How stupid do you think I am?
事实上 你真是头蠢猪
Pretty damn stupid, actually.
什么?
Excuse me?
我的确在演戏 女人
This is a setup, lady.
屋外停着辆面包车
There's a van sittin' right outside.
这房子装了窃听器 已经被警察包围了
The room is bugged. The place is surrounded by cops.
所以现在 你把枪放下
So now you wanna put that gun down,
然后我们把事情理理清
and we'll work something out.
他们的目标不是你 他们要捉的是你丈夫
They don't care about you. They want your husband.
这箱子里有个追踪器 你所要做的
There's a tracer in the case. All you had to do
就是把你丈夫的藏身之处说出来
was take it back to wherever your hubby's hiding out.
你以为我真的会相信
You really except me to believe
你是警方派来的?
that you're working with the police?
如果这地方被包围了
If this place is surrounded,
为什么没一个人进来救你?
how come no one came to save you?
我不需要救援
I don't need saving,
因为你会听话
'cause you're gonna do the right thing
乖乖把枪放下 但如果你不放
and put that gun down. But if you don't,
那么 我也有办法
well, then all I gotta do is say the magic work,
让那扇门为我打开
and that door busts open.
你真是个蹩脚的骗子
You're a lousy con man.
Lafleur啊
Lafleur.
"La"什么?
"La" what?
警察! 把枪放下!
Police! Drop the gun!
- 手背过来 - 我们进来得早了点儿吧?
- Behind your back. - Cuttin' it a little close, huh?
实在没办法啊
Only way to cut it.
把你的衣服穿起来 Jim
Put your damn clothes on, Jim.
没问题 好搭档
You got it, partner.
- 你是警察? - 惊讶吧
- You're a cop? - Surprise.
走吧 快走
Let's go. Move.
迷失 第6季第8集
你就住在这里?
Is this where you lived?
嗯
Yeah.
那是什么?
What is that?
它是我的一切
It's all I had.
嗯 各位 听我说!
All right, everybody, listen up!
过来 围成圈
Come on in. Gather 'round.
我知道你们都累极了
I know that everyone is tired.
我们度过了...
It was a...
一个漫长而悲惨的夜晚
a long and traumatic night for all of us.
我知道 你们肯定满腹疑问
And you all have got a lot of questions, I know,
我会尽力作答
And I will make myself available to answer them.
但现在 我们得继续出发
But right now we need to keep moving.
- 要抓住白天的优势 - 我们想知道
- We have to take advantage of the daylight. - We wanna know
留在寺庙的人都怎样了
what happened to the people who stayed behind at the temple.
黑烟杀了他们
The black smoke killed them.
嘿
Hey.
我知道那里发生的一切 可怕至极
I know that what happened back there was really scary.
但一切都结束了
But it's over.
你们和我在一起
You're with me now,
我承诺 会让大家相安无事的
and I promise that I'm gonna take care of you.
好了
Okay.
我们出发吧
Alright, let's move out.
听上去 你这一晚上过得可不安生
Sounds like you had a hell of a night.
没错
Yeah.
Jack Hurley 还有其他人...
Jack, Hurley, the rest of 'em...
他们都安然无恙地从庙里出来了么?
They make it out of the temple all right?
我回来的时候 看到他们离开
I saw them leaving on my way back.
- 那Miles呢? - 我不知道他怎样了
- What about Miles? - I don't know what happened to him.
那你现在和Locke是一边的了?
So you're with Locke now?
我保持中立 Kate
I ain't with anybody, Kate.
你好 请问是Anthony Cooper吗?
Hello. Is this Anthony Cooper?
嗨 Cooper先生 我是洛杉矶警署的James Ford探员
Hi, Mr. Cooper. This is Detective James Ford, L.A.P.D.
嗯 我们发现了一批无主钱物
Yeah, we've discovered some unclaimed property
估计是你名下财产
that might belong to you.
你能证实自己在1976年 曾到过阿拉巴马州吗?
Can you verify you were in Alabama in 1976?
啊哈
Uh-huh.
好的 谢谢 抱歉打扰 再见
Okay, thanks. Sorry to have taken up your time. Bye-bye.
能请Anthony Cooper接下电话吗?
Can I speak with Anthony Cooper?
抱歉 我稍后再打来
Sorry. I'm gonna have to call you back.
Anthony Cooper是谁?
Who's Anthony Cooper?
我偶然认识的一个老头
Old buddy I ran into.
- 他说 他可以帮我弄到几张湖人队的入场券 - 真不错
- Said he could hook me up with some Laker tickets. - That's cool.
我说 你... 你是在棕榈泉见到他的?
What, did you... you see him in Palm Springs?
什么?
What?
棕榈泉? 你上周出差去的地方啊?
Palm Springs? Your trip last weekend?
嗯 我都记不清了
Yeah. It's a blur.
阳光普照 Mai Tais鸡尾酒香飘万里
Too much sunshine. Too many Mai Tais.
嗯 振作一下 你今晚有个约会 兄弟
Well, get it together, because you got a date tonight, pal.
和谁约会?
Date with who?
我一个朋友 是我爸在博物馆的同事
Friend of mine, works with my dad at the museum.
她可是个好女孩
She's great.
呃 如果她真的那么好 你干嘛不和她约会?
Well, if she's so great, why don't you go out with her?
嘿 我有女朋友了 你想怎样 Jim?
Hey, I got a girlfriend. What is your deal, Jim?
孤独地老死?
Do you wanna die alone?
好吧 我去和她见面
All right, look, I go out with her,
- 你可以消停了吧? - 给我一张湖人队的入场券
- you gonna leave me alone? - Throw in one of those Laker tickets,
我绝不多说一句废话
hell, yes, I will.
听我说 我正在到处找这家伙
Look, I'm already pulling strings with this guy.
就是 呃...
It's just, uh...
我不知道我能不能再弄到一张票
I don't know if I can get another seat.
你可以把实话告诉我的...
You know you can tell me the truth...
什么也别隐瞒
About anything.
伙计 你在对我撒谎吗?
Are you lying to me, man?
我干嘛要撒谎?
Why the hell would I lie?
再走一里地 就空旷了
About a quarter mile ahead, there's a clearing.
我们会在那儿扎营 大家记得补充水源
We'll make camp there. Everybody fill up on water.
大概还有两三天的路程
We might be there a couple of days.
两三天?
A couple of days?
我以为你说我们翻过这座山就好
I thought you said we were gettin' off this rock.
的确是
We are.
什么时候?
When?
要不要换个地方 私下谈谈?
Maybe we should talk about this in private?
好啊 走吧
Great. Let's go.
我希望你不要打断我的话
I wish you hadn't interrupted me.
抱歉 我是个粗人
I'm sorry. I forgot my manners.
没事
I forgive ya.
寺庙那儿发生什么事了?
What happened back at the temple?
你怎么知道 要去把大家从黑烟手中救出来?
How'd you know to rescue everybody from that smoke thing?
我没有救他们
I didn't rescue them.
我就是那黑烟
I'm the smoke thing.
你是说 是你把那些人都杀掉的?
You telling me you killed all those people?
我给了他们安然逃离的机会
I gave them the opportunity to leave peacefully,
- 可他们视如敝屐 - 为什么?
- and they didn't take it. - Why not?
因为他们坚信
Because they're convinced
他们能把岛守得固若金汤 让我无处下手
that they're protecting the island from me,
事实上 我只想离开这里
when, in fact, all I wanna do is leave.
所以我不杀掉他们 就会被他们杀掉
So it's either kill or be killed.
我可不想死
And I don't want to be killed.
我们要坐船?
We goin' on a boat ride?
是你要坐船
You are.
去哪里?
Where?
九头蛇岛
Hydra Island.
九头蛇岛上有什么?
What's on Hydra Island?
飞机 Ajira航空的那架航班
The plane. The Ajira flight.
把你朋友带回来的那架飞机
The same plane that brought your friends back.
不幸地是 他们身边还有其他人
Unfortunately, they didn't come alone.
我有理由相信
And I have reason to believe that
个别乘客想对我们不利
some of the other passengers mean to do us all harm.
所以我想让你去那边 探探虚实
So I want you to go over there and do some recon.
听上去真安全哦
Well, that sounds safe.
- 你不会有事的 - 是吗? 那如果我
- You'll be fine. - Yeah? Well, what am I supposed to do
碰上了一个想加害我的人 可怎么办啊?
if I run into somebody who wants to do me harm?
- 我不担心这个 - 哦 你不担心 是吧?
- I'm not worried about that. - Oh, you're not, huh?
没错 因为你是我所遇到的 最会说谎的人了
No, because you are the best liar I ever met.
把该说的话都说给他们听
You tell 'em whatever you need to tell 'em
取得他们的信任 探明他们的一切
to gain their trust, find out everything you can about them,
然后回到这儿
and then get back here.
我再做一遍有什么意义啊?
Why exactly am I doing this again?
还有什么好想的呢 James?
Why do you think, James?
我们登上飞机 离开这个岛
We get on the plane, we fly off this island,
就永远不会再回来了
and we never look back.
来吧
Come on.
喂?
Yeah?
Miles 这个姑娘长什么样来着?
Miles, what's this girl look like again?
红发 你看到几... 几个红头发的啊?
She's a redhead. How many... how many redheads do you see?
- 知道了 - 对她温柔点...
- Roger that. - Be nice to her...
好了 知道了
Yeah, yeah.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
你是Charlotte吧?
Would you be Charlotte?
没错
I most certainly am.
很高兴见到你 女士
Well, it's a pleasure to meet you, ma'am.
谢谢
Thank you.
考古学 对吧?
Archaeology, huh?
有什么问题吗?
What's wrong with archaeology?
没什么
Nothin'.
我只是在想象你待在房间里
I just figured you'd be stuck in a room somewhere
给古董除灰的样子
dusting off antiques.
没有啦 其实我更多是在野外工作
No, I actually get to travel quite a bit,
去一些遥远又浪漫的地方
to far off and romantic places.
真的吗?
Really?
你喜欢像"夺宝奇兵"里演的那样吗?
What, you like an Indiana Jones or something?
是的 我就喜欢那种感觉
Yes. I'm exactly like Indiana Jones.
你也有根鞭子?
You got a whip?
或许吧
Maybe.
呃 说说你吧?
So, um, what about you?
- 说什么呢? - 你怎么会当上警察的?
- What about me? - Why did you become a cop?
你看过Steve Mcqueen演的"浑身是胆"吗?
You ever seen "Bullitt" Steve Mcqueen flick?
没有
No.
那我也就无从谈起了
Well, then I won't even bore you with an explanation.
拜托啦 James 别拿你应付其他发问的女孩那套
Okay, do me a favor, James, and don't treat me like
来搪塞我
all the other girls who ask you.
告诉我实话吧
Tell me the truth.
好吧...
Well...
我想我... 是到了人生的一个分水岭
I guess I... got to a point in my life
要么去做坏蛋 要么就去做警察
where I was either gonna come a criminal or a cop.
所以我选择了当警察
So I chose cop.
怎么啦?
What?
你懂的
You know what.
在没有那根鞭子的情况下 这过程真还不赖啊
Well, not bad, considering we didn't have that whip.
下次带过来
Bring it next time.
想喝水吗?
You want some water?
嗯 拿点过来吧
Mm-hmm. Yes, please.
介意我借一件T恤吗?
You mind if I borrow a T-shirt?
自己去拿吧 右边上面的抽屉里
Help yourself. Top drawer on the right.
谢谢
Thanks.
你他妈的在干嘛?
What the hell are you doing?
呃 我在找T恤啊
Um, I was just looking for T-shirt.
- 你看到什么了? - 没什么 就是...有张照片掉出来了
- What did you see? - Nothing, just that you had... that picture fell out,
- 我正准备放回去 - 你看到什么了?!
- and I was just trying to put it back. - What did you see?!
- 没什么! 我什么也没看到 - 滚出去
- Nothing! I didn't see anything. - Get the hell out.
- James 听我解释 - 出去!
- James, just let me explain. - Get out!
嘿
Hey.
Kate啊
Kate.
你相信Locke吗?
Do you believe Locke?
你指哪方面?
What do you mean?
他说他可以带我们离岛
That he can get us off the island.
没错 我相信他
Yes, I believe him.
Sayid 你还好吧?
Sayid, are you all right?
不好
No.
Claire啊! Sayid啊!
Claire! Sayid!
Sayid 快来啊! 停...
Sayid, please! St...
你在干什么啊?!
What are you doing?!
- 她把他带走了! 她把Aaron带走了! - Claire 你那会儿失踪了 Kate找不到你
- She took him! She took Aaron! - Claire, you had disappeared. Kate couldn't find you.
- 她做了她能做的一切 - 她带走了Aaron! 她凭什么那么做啊！
- She did what she had to do. - She took Aaron! She can't just do that!
你这么做是不对的
This is completely inappropriate.
懂吗?
All right?
现在... 你到那边去 我马上就去找你详谈
Now... you go over there. I'll deal with you in a minute.
去吧
Go.
你没事吧?
You all right?
不 我很不好!
No, I'm not all right!
嘿! 站住!
Hey! Stop!
- 别! 哦! - 不许动!
- No! Oh! - Don't move!
请别伤害我!
Please don't hurt me!
你究竟是谁?
Who the hell are you?
我是唯一的幸存者
I'm the only one left.
打扰一下 先生?
Excuse me, sir?
我在问你我弟弟的事情
I asked you about my brother.
跟你说过了 再等一分钟
I told you. I'll be with you in a minute.
嘿 呃 我在找我的弟弟
Hey, uh, I'm looking for my brother.
呃 他因为藏毒 在机场被捕
Uh, he was arrested at the airport on a drug charge.
对不起 这不在我的职责范围内
Sorry. Not my department.
早上好啊 阳光男孩
Mornin', sunshine.
跟我来
Come with me.
- 哇! 你他妈的... - 闭嘴!
- Whoa! What the hell is your... - Shut up!
- 你没别的话要说吗? - 什么?!
- Is there something you wanna tell me? - What?!
你不想说些什么吗?
Is there something you wanna tell me?
听着 她不该打开那个抽屉的
Look, she opened the wrong drawer.
你在说什么啊?
What the hell are you talking about?
我想知道 你在澳大利亚到底干了些什么
I wanna know what you were doing in Australia
就是你对我说你在棕榈泉的时候
when you told me you were in Palm Springs.
我查了你的信用卡记录 我知道你去了悉尼
I ran your credit card. I know you went to Sydney.
大洋航空公司 往返票
Oceanic. Round trip.
两天前 你搭乘815航班回来的
You took flight 815 back 2 days ago.
你查我的信用卡记录干什么啊?
What the hell are you doin' running my credit card?
你对我撒谎了!
You lied to me!
我们应该相互信任的
We're supposed to trust each other.
所以 Jim...
So, Jim...
你在澳大利亚做了些什么啊?
What were you doing in Australia?
与你无关
That's none of your damn business.
你知道吗?
You know what?
你说对了
You're right,
因为我不再是你的拍档了
because I'm not your partner anymore.
口渴吗?
You thirsty?
渴得很
Very.
我叫Sawyer
I'm Sawyer.
啊
Ahh.
我叫Zoe 简直无法相信还有人活着
I'm Zoe. I can't believe there's anybody left alive.
我还以为我认识飞机上的每一个人
I thought I knew everybody on the plane.
我不是这架飞机上的
I didn't come on this plane.
- 那你是乘哪架飞机来的啊? - 说来话长
- What plane did you come on? - Long story.
这儿发生什么事了? 怎么死了这么多人?
What the hell happened here? What killed all those people?
我...
I...
我们... 我们的飞机失事了
We... We crashed here,
大家还等着有人来...
and we were all just waiting for...
有人来救我们
someone to rescue us.
我正出去捡柴禾的时候
I was out collecting wood
突然听到...
when I heard...
尖叫声
screaming.
尖叫声?
Screaming?
当...
When...
当我回来的时候...
When I came back...
他们... 他们都已经死了
they were... they were all dead.
我花了两天时间 把这些尸体拖到一起
I spent the last two days dragging their bodies up here.
我不想让他们就这么曝晒在太阳底下
I didn't feel it was right to leave them out there in the sun.
你一个人吗?
Are you alone?
不是 我和一群人要回主岛
No. I'm with a group of people back on the main island.
- 我可以带你过去 - 哦 感谢上帝
- I can take you back there. - Oh, thank God.
信我一句吧
Trust me,
上帝才不管这事呢
God's got nothing to do with it.
对不起 Kate
I'm sorry, Kate.
什么?
Excuse me?
我得为Claire的行为向你道歉
I have to take responsibility for Claire's behavior.
我告诉她 是The Others带走了她的孩子
I was the one who told her that The Others had her baby.
你为什么要这么跟她说?
Why would you tell her that?
你有仇人吗?
Have you ever had an enemy?
让你憎恨万分的仇人?
Someone that you needed to hate?
突然感到有力量了 是吧?
Very powerful, isn't it?
失去Aaron以后 Claire几近崩溃了
Claire was devastated without Aaron.
她需要一些...
She needed something to...
一些让她活下去的动力 所以...
something to keep her going, so...
我给她制造了假想敌
I gave her something to hate.
当你告诉她真相的时候
And then when you told her the truth,
所有那些感觉 所有... 所有那些愤怒
all those feelings, all... all that anger
那些支撑她这么久的动力...
that she'd been holding on to for so long...
全都消失了
It had to go somewhere.
真有远见...
Very insightful...
出自一个死人之口
Coming from a dead man.
嗯
Mm.
人无完人
Well, nobody's perfect.
很抱歉发生了这样的事
I'm sorry that this happened.
我保证只要你给她些时间
And I'm sure if you give her time,
一切都会好起来的
everything will be all right.
之前我答应过 我会确保大家的安全
I promised before that I would keep everyone safe,
这话对你也同样适用 Kate
and that means you, too, Kate.
Sawyer去哪儿了?
Where did Sawyer go?
我会告诉你的
I'll show you.
觉得它还能飞吗?
Think that thing'll still fly?
我不知道 估计得费点儿工夫
I don't know. It'll take a bit of work
还得找个知道如何... 如何来操作的人才行
and someone who knows how to... how to do it.
我... 我猜你没有遇到过飞行员吧?
I... I take it you haven't come across the pilot?
是的 夫人
No, ma'am.
你刚刚说 有多少人和你在一块儿的?
How many people did you say were with you?
二十来个吧
Couple dozen.
他们都是和你乘同一架飞机来的?
Did they all come on the same plane with you?
有些是 但不全是
Some, not all.
你们的飞机是什么时候失事的?
When did you crash?
很久以前
Long time ago.
你们都有枪吗?
Do you all have guns?
我是说 不管是谁杀了这些人
I mean, whoever killed those people back there,
他们... 他们可能会再回来
they... they might come back.
哦 我们有很多枪
Yeah, we got plenty of guns.
你抓住那头好吗?
You wanna grab that end?
你说你要去哪?
Where'd you say you were headed?
什么?
What's that?
你的航班 目的地是哪儿?
Your flight. Where were you going?
哦 呃...
Oh. Uh...
关岛
Guam.
谁在关岛么?
What's in Guam?
我男朋友
My boyfriend.
你戏演得真好 宝贝 但是还没好到滴水不漏
You're good, sweetheart, but you ain't that good.
- 你在说什么? - 你是谁?
- What are you talking about? - Who are you?
放下你的武器! 马上放下!
Drop your weapon down! Drop it now!
你的名字Zoe 是真的吗?
Your name even Zoe?
你是叫Sawyer吗?
Is yours Sawyer?
跪下!
Down on your knees!
好的 好的 我很听话的
All right, all right. You got me.
带我去见你们的头儿
Take me to your leader.
小岛在那边... 我派Sawyer去那了
That island over there... that's where I sent Sawyer.
你只需要告诉我
You could've just told me
你派他去的是 那个我们曾被困在牢笼里的小岛
that you sent him to the island where we were locked in cages.
你没必要带我来这里
You didn't have to bring me down here.
是的 但是那时候我没机会对你说
Sure, but then I wouldn't have gotten to talk to you.
你把我当死人
You referred to me as a dead man.
我不是死人
I am not a dead man.
我知道你的感受 Kate
I know what you're feeling, Kate.
我知道你的经历
I know what you're going through.
你怎么知道的?
How do you know that?
因为...
Because...
我妈妈疯了
my mother was crazy.
很久很久以前 在我...
A long time ago, before I...
就像... 这么大的时候
looked... like this,
像所有人一样 我有一个妈妈
I had a mother, just like everyone.
她是个精神错乱的女人
She was a very disturbed woman.
正因为如此...
And as a result of that...
我的成长之路异常艰辛...
I had some growing pains...
问题是 我还得努力杀出一条血路
problems that I'm still trying to work my way through.
如果能...
Problems that...
避免... 这些问题
could h... have been avoided,
如今会大不相同
had things been different.
为什么要跟我说这些?
Why are you telling me this?
因为现在... Aaron...
Because now... Aaron...
也有一个疯妈妈
has a crazy mother, too.
下去 他在等你
Get in. He's waiting for you.
我不是担心我自己
It's not me I'm worried about.
我只是不知道 如果你和妈妈
I just don't know what I'd do
发生什么事 我应该做什么
if anything ever happened to you and ma.
不管怎样 我们不会有事的
Anyway, nothing's gonna happen to us.
至少今天不会
Not today, anyway.
这就是你生活的方式
It's the way you live this life,
每天一次
Each day one at a time.
如果你一辈子都在
Now if you spend your whole life
杞人忧天
worrying about something that's gonna happen,
在你意识到之前 你的生活已经结束了
before you know it, your life's over
你一辈子都只是在痛苦地担心
and you spent an awful lot of it just worrying.
嘿 你听见没?
Hey, you hear that?
这才是生活的全部...
That's what life's all about...
笑对生活 彼此相爱
laughing and loving each other,
知道当人们死的时候 他们并没有消失
and knowing that people aren't really gone when they die.
美好的回忆支撑着我们
We have all the good memories to sustain us
直到再次相见
until we see 'em again.
想要不害怕 很难 爸爸
It's hard not being afraid, pa.
我知道 宝贝儿
I know, sweetheart
我知道
I know.
你真会开玩笑
You've got to be joking.
我能进去吗?
May I come in?
- 当然不能 - 为什么?
- Absolutely not. - Why not?
你不是吧 凌晨3点把我踢出来
You don't get to kick me out at 3:00 in the morning
然后第二天过来
and then come 'round the next day
带着一副小狗似的可怜眼神 和一朵忧郁的向日葵
with puppy dog eyes and a sad sunflower.
听着 我不知道
Look, I don't know
你是因为孤寂 或内疚 还是完全疯了
if you're just lonely or guilty or completely mad.
但是你知道吗? 我不在乎 是你搞砸的一切
But you know what? I don't care. You blew it.
- 你把什么锁在这里? - 不关你事 快走
- What you got in here? - None of your business. Keep moving.
进来
Come.
他来了 老大
He's here, sir.
谢谢 Zoe
Thanks, Zoe.
能让我们单独待会儿吗?
Would you leave us, please?
没问题
Of course.
你好啊 Ford先生
Hello, Mr. Ford.
我叫Charles Widmore
My name is Charles Widmore.
- 你知道我是谁吗? - 我当然知道
- Do you know who I am? - Of course I do.
你派了艘船到岛上 还下令手下杀光我们
You're the fella sent a freighter to the island, and order the guys to kill us all.
真可怜...
It's sad, really...
你知道的太少了
How little you actually know.
哦 我知道是你们杀了所有人
Well, I know you murdered all them people out there
- 然后把他们扔到沟里 - 我们没杀那些人
- and dropped 'em in the ditch. - We didn't murder those people.
但是我也不指望你能相信
But I don't expect you to believe that.
很好 因为我根本就不信
Good, 'cause I don't.
那你跟我说说 谁派你来这个岛上的?
So why don't you tell me what brought you over to this island?
John Locke派我来的
John Locke sent me.
John Locke已经死了
John Locke's dead.
我想我俩都知道 我所说这个人
I think we both know the guy I'm talking about
不是真的Locke
is not really Locke.
我们做个交易吧 老大
So here's the deal, chief.
我回去告诉他 海岸上什么都没有
I'll go back over there and tell him the coast is clear,
我连人影都没发现
that I didn't find anybody.
然后我把那个老头带到你门口
Then I'll bring the old man right to your doorstep.
接着你就可以杀了他
Then you can kill him.
交换条件是什么 James?
And what do you want in exchange, James?
第一... 我带回来的人...
One... the people I come back with...
我船上的人...
the people on my boat...
别动他们 一根毫毛都不能碰
don't get touched, not even a hair on their head.
第二...
And two...
你让我们安全地离开小岛
you give us safe passage off the island.
我凭什么信任你?
How do I know I can trust you?
因为我信任你
Same way I know I can trust you.
那么...
So...
我们达成协议了吗?
do we have an agreement?
我想是的
I suppose we do.
Kate啊
Kate.
我...
I...
我只是...
I just, um...
我只想说 对不起
I... I just wanna say I'm sorry.
我不知道我为什么那么做
I don't know why I did that.
我知道你做的一切 都是因为你关心我
I know everything you did was just 'cause you care about me
和Aaron
and about Aaron.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你照顾他
Thank you for taking care of him.
对不起
I'm sorry.
非常非常地 对不起
I'm so, so sorry.
好了
It's okay.
没事
好了啊
It's okay.
怎么样?
How'd go?
你不是真的派我去那儿
You didn't really send me over there
找飞机上的乘客吧?
to find passengers from that plane, did you?
不是
No.
如果你感兴趣
Well, in case you're interested,
他们都死了
they're all dead.
哦 真惨啊
Well, that's terrible.
发生了什么?
What happened?
我不知道
I don't know.
James 你知道什么?
Well, what do you know, James?
我知道那个小岛有个人
I know there's a man over there on that island
如果不打一仗 他不会让我们登机的
that ain't gonna let us get on that plane without a fight.
他叫Widmore 驾着一艘潜艇来的
Came over on a sub. Name's Widmore.
Charles Widmore吗?
Charles Widmore?
哦 我想你们认识
Well, I guess y'all know each other.
他不是一个人
He ain't alone.
至少有6个全副武装的同伙
I counted at least six armed compadres with him,
还不算潜艇上的工作人员
not to mention whatever crew's on that sub.
那有个锁着的房间... 有东西藏在里面
There's a locked room on there... somethin' they're hiding.
他们还在架设电缆塔 就像在New Otherton的那些塔一样
And they're settin' up pylons, like the ones at New Otherton.
你知道的...
You know...
那些塔能抵御黑烟
the ones that keep out that smoke thing.
你跟他们怎么说我的?
And what did you tell them about me?
我告诉他们
I told them
我会告诉你那岸上没人 然后带你过去
I'd tell you the coast was clear and bring you back with me.
带你径直走进他们的陷阱
Walk you right into their trap.
那样 他们可以杀了你...
That way, they could kill you...
这意味着 当我们改变进攻计划的话
which means they'll be caught with their pants down
他们来不及反应 就会束手待毙
when we change our plan of attack.
James 我感谢你的忠心
I appreciate your loyalty, James.
你说过要送我离开这个岛
You said you were gonna get me off this island.
说话要算话
Deal's a deal.
- 你在这干嘛? - 上车
- What are you doing here? - Get in the car.
Sawyer是谁?
Who's Sawyer?
我9岁的时候
When I was 9 years old,
我爸杀了我妈 然后他自杀了
my father shot my mother, and then he killed himself.
Sawyer是罪魁祸首
Sawyer was the reason why.
他是个骗子
He was a grifter.
大骗子
Con man.
自从我大学毕业以后
I've been hunting him down
一直在追捕他
since the day I left the academy.
我在澳大利亚追查到一个线索
I chased down a lead in Australia,
是一个名字... Anthony Cooper
got a name... Anthony Cooper.
我搜索这个名字 得到一堆叫Anthony Cooper的人
I ran the name. I got a list of Anthony Coopers,
于是我挨个调查他们
and I've been calling them.
当我找到要找的那个...
And when I find the right one...
我会杀了他
I'm gonna kill him.
为什么以前 你一点都没跟我说过?
Why didn't you tell me any of this?
我知道你一直想劝我放弃
I knew you'd try and talk me out of it.
没错
Damn right.
好极了
Fair enough.
喔! 我的车!
Whoa! My car!
嘿!
Hey!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
晚饭吃什么?
What's for dinner?
野兔
Rabbit.
应该没问题
I think.
很好 我正饿着
Good. I'm starving.
你在为Locke跑腿干什么?
What are you doing running errands for Locke?
我不给任何人跑腿
I ain't runnin' errands for nobody.
他说他派你去另一个岛
He said he sent you over to the other island.
你找到飞机了吗?
Did you find the plane?
嗯
Yeah.
然而并不是只有飞机
And that ain't the only thing over there.
一个叫Widmore的家伙在海滩上扎营
A guy named Widmore set up camp on the beach,
带了一队人...
got a whole team with him...
全副武装
guys with guns.
他们为Locke而来
They're here for Locke.
那你要做什么?
So what are you gonna do?
我要让他们打一仗
I'm gonna let them fight it out.
当他们全力交战 无暇他顾的时候...
And while they got their hands full with each other...
我们离开这个见鬼的小岛
you and me are gettin' the hell off this island.
即使我们能上得了飞机 谁会开呢?
Even if we could get on that plane, who's gonna fly it?
我们不坐飞机 雀斑女
We ain't taking the plane, Freckles.
我们坐潜艇走
We're taking the sub.